<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tyler&#39;s Project Blog</title>
    <link>http://tylerengle.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tyler&#39;s Project Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 14:02:17 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tylerengle.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Website</title>
      <link>http://tylerengle.xyz/posts/2020-11-26-setting-up-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 14:02:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tylerengle.xyz/posts/2020-11-26-setting-up-website/</guid>
      <description>The tools used to design this website are Hugo and Nginx. I want a static site so Hugo is perfect for that. I chose Nginx because I want to lean more about it. I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this website on a VPS using Centos8. I&amp;rsquo;m designing the website using vscode on Arch Linux.
There&amp;rsquo;s a few things I want to do here:
 Set up the website so it can be accessed from the web Add SSL certificate Harden Nginx settings  Setting up the website The first thing is to create a new website with Hugo in the current directory on my own machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://tylerengle.xyz/posts/2020-11-25-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tylerengle.xyz/posts/2020-11-25-new-website/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a mostly tech blog. I created this to document my projects and ideas. I keep forgetting things and keep re-researching them. Hopefully this will help. I&amp;rsquo;m also hoping to improve my technical writing.
I&amp;rsquo;ll get more stuff up here eventually, maybe mess with the theme. Probably could make an email with my own domain at some point. More projects to add.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on setting up Pfsense at home, but waiting on some more ethernet to attach a Unifi Lite AP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
